{
    "id": "cec37a235df643efa54a96148fb2c0f0",
    "title": "Infinitive or gerund exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "a44924bddcfe4760a70708a676cb86bd",
            "title": "Infinitive Or Gerund Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I still miss ………………… in Singapore.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to live",
                        "living",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I enjoy …………………. in the sea.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "swimming",
                        "to swim"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He avoided ………………….. his ex-girlfriend.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "meeting",
                        "to meet"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "You promised ………………… it by Monday.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to finish",
                        "finishing"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She expected ………………… the job.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to get",
                        "getting"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Would you like …………………. with me?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "come",
                        "coming",
                        "to come"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "She taught me how ………………… it.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "do",
                        "to do"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I don’t feel like ………………… out tonight.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to go",
                        "going"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Would you mind ………………….. the window?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to open",
                        "opening"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Do you mind my …………………. late?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "coming",
                        "come",
                        "to come"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}